{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Who is the current captain of the Indian cricket team?",
      "option1": "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "option2": "Sunil Chhetri",
      "option3": "Virat Kohli",
      "option4": "Rohit Shrama",
      "correctAnswer": "Virat Kohli"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Who is the current captain of the Indian football team?",
      "option1": "Baichung Bhutia",
      "option2": "Sunil Chhetri",
      "option3": "Sandesh Jhingan",
      "option4": "Rohit Shrama",
      "correctAnswer": "Sunil Chhetri"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "When did India win the first cricket world cup?",
      "option1": "1996",
      "option2": "1983",
      "option3": "2011",
      "option4": "2019",
      "correctAnswer": "1983"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Which tennis player has the best record on clay courts?",
      "option1": "Rafael Nadal",
      "option2": "Novak Djokovic",
      "option3": "Roger Federer",
      "option4": "Andy Murray",
      "correctAnswer": "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Which one of the following football clubs is the oldest",
      "option1": "Real Madrid",
      "option2": "FC Barcelona",
      "option3": "Mohun Bagan",
      "option4": "Liverpool FC",
      "correctAnswer": "Mohun Bagan"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Ryder cup is related to which sports?",
      "option1": "Polo",
      "option2": "Golf",
      "option3": "Badminton",
      "option4": "Tennis",
      "correctAnswer": "Golf"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Pen Holder grip is used in which of the following sports?",
      "option1": "Polo",
      "option2": "Golf",
      "option3": "Badminton",
      "option4": "Table Tennis",
      "correctAnswer": "Table Tennis"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "When was the last time the Olympic salute was used?",
      "option1": "1956",
      "option2": "1948",
      "option3": "1974",
      "option4": "1924",
      "correctAnswer": "1948"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "With which sport is Dutee Chand associated?",
      "option1": "Sprint 100m",
      "option2": "Long Jump",
      "option3": "High Jump",
      "option4": "Discus Throw",
      "correctAnswer": "Sprint 100m"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Who had founded the International Olympic Committee in 1894?",
      "option1": "Jacques Rogge",
      "option2": "Demetrios Vikelas",
      "option3": "Pierre de Coubertin",
      "option4": "Henry Kissinger",
      "correctAnswer": "Pierre de Coubertin"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "Holkar Trophy is associated with which sport?",
      "option1": "Bridge",
      "option2": "Cricket",
      "option3": "Football",
      "option4": "Basketball",
      "correctAnswer": "Bridge"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "The first Indian to cross seven important seas by swimming is",
      "option1": "Amrendra Singh",
      "option2": "Bula Chaudhury",
      "option3": "Yuri Gagarin",
      "option4": "Junko Taibei",
      "correctAnswer": "Bula Chaudhury"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "Who has scored the most goals for India?",
      "option1": "Sunil Chhetri",
      "option2": "Udanta Singh",
      "option3": "Balwant Singh",
      "option4": "Farukh Chowdary",
      "correctAnswer": "Sunil Chhetri"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "The 2017 Indian Premier League (IPL 2017) first match on 5 April, 2017 was held in ?",
      "option1": "Bengaluru",
      "option2": "Mumbai",
      "option3": "Hyderabad",
      "option4": "Delhi",
      "correctAnswer": "Hyderabad"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "Against which team did Virender Sehwag make his one day international debut",
      "option1": "New Zealand",
      "option2": "England",
      "option3": "Pakistan",
      "option4": "Australia",
      "correctAnswer": "Pakistan"
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "The cricket stadium 'Gabba' is in which state in Australia",
      "option1": "Sydney",
      "option2": "Melbourne",
      "option3": "Queensland",
      "option4": "Brisbane",
      "correctAnswer": "Brisbane"
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "How long are professional Golf Tour Players allotted per shot?",
      "option1": "35s",
      "option2": "40s",
      "option3": "45s",
      "option4": "53s",
      "correctAnswer": "45s"
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "'Hopman cup'  is related to which sports?",
      "option1": "Badminton",
      "option2": "Lawn Tennis",
      "option3": "Baseball",
      "option4": "Football",
      "correctAnswer": "Lawn Tennis"
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "Which among these cricket bowlers has taken 10 wickets in a single inning in a test match",
      "option1": "Jawagal Srinath",
      "option2": "Anil Kumble",
      "option3": "Shane warne",
      "option4": "Zaheer Khan",
      "correctAnswer": "Anil Kumble"
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "question": "Who was the first Indian to qualify for olympics?",
      "option1": "Mary Kom",
      "option2": "PT Usha",
      "option3": "Shiny Abraham",
      "option4": "Jyotirmony Sikdar",
      "correctAnswer": "PT Usha"
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "question": "Who is known as Mr. 360 in cricket?",
      "option1": "Virat Kohli",
      "option2": "MS Dhoni",
      "option3": "AB de Villiers",
      "option4": "Steve Smith",
      "correctAnswer": "AB de Villiers"
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "question": "Badminton is national game of which country?",
      "option1": "USA",
      "option2": "Bhutan",
      "option3": "India",
      "option4": "Indonesia",
      "correctAnswer": "Indonesia"
    },
    {
      "number": 23,
      "question": "P.V. Sindhu defeated which player in the finals to win her maiden India Open Super Series title on 2 April 2017 ?",
      "option1": "Wang Yihan",
      "option2": "Carolina Marin",
      "option3": " Greysia Polii",
      "option4": "Sung Ji-Hyun",
      "correctAnswer": "Carolina Marin"
    },
    {
      "number": 24,
      "question": "Who won the FIFA World cup 2018?",
      "option1": "Croatia",
      "option2": "France",
      "option3": "Germany",
      "option4": "Spain",
      "correctAnswer": "France"
    },
    {
      "number": 25,
      "question": "Who are winners of 2016 Kabaddi World Cup ?",
      "option1": "Iran",
      "option2": "Korea",
      "option3": "India",
      "option4": "Bangladesh",
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    }
  ]
}
